know better than you. Moses was the greatest prophet, right? Yes. And he said? Well, until
Yeshua. No, that's not true. Yeshua was Moses. Yeshua is the prophet Moses foretold. Yeah.
Yeah, and Yeshua was learning from Moses. That means that Moses is greater. Moses was Yeshua's
teacher. Moses was before. Yeshua did not learn directly from Moses. Yes, he did. He learned
from the Nazarenes and his mother and his father and his rabbis. Look, it says that the rabbis
are priests and they're also corrupt. How can you say that? Huh? Yeah, and he called them
out for it. He called them paritzim, Medina paritzim, for committing sacrifices. He said,
go and learn what this means. Hosea 6-6. Bull? What is bull what? What's bull? What did I
say that was bull? He doesn't say jerk. You read the scriptures. That's why. Hosea. Hosea 6-6. I desire
chesed. Mercy, not sacrifice. I know you don't. I can't. It's bull. I can't explain it for
you, but I can't understand it for you. Look, exactly. You show us the. No, I can explain
it for you, but I can't make you understand it. How can you explain something you don't
understand? I do understand it. God created creatures for their own life and they are being
murdered here and it's wrong. Because it's wrong. Because God created you as a creature,
no? We should murder you. No, no creature should be murdered. No, do not kill. Moses, do not
No, there are words in the Pentateuch that are from God. But the Lion Pen of the Scribes...
The five books of Torah are from God. The five books of Torah are from God. The five books of Torah are from God.
I'll tell you how we know that's the truth.
Not all of them, no. All five of them, all five of them, no, yes, no, yes, there has been...
Jeremiah did that? No, no, no, he went from the first temple, he was in the first temple.
Yeah, and that's the beginning. No, they did.
Oh, they did. Why did he stop that?
He did. Read Jeremiah. Read Jeremiah.
Because you've got to weigh it against God's ontology of the prophets.
Well, the first temple was destroyed.
You weigh it against God's ontology of the prophets?
Many, many prophets.
God is omnipotent, omnichesent, all-powerful, all-knowing, so any being that is all of those things would not murder his own creation.
Oh, I read them all.
Why can't you decide what you want to do in all of them?
Because he's omnibenevolent.
So he can't decide to be one of those Christians.
All good.
It's more accurate than yours.
Murder and goodness are antithetical.
I'll read that, too.
It's not murder to eat either.
I read everything.
It is murder.
Yeah, I read everything.
What were chickens made for?
Clever.
They were created for their own purpose.
Because we have a relationship with them and we name them.
What's their purpose?
They have their own purpose.
What do you define what is it?
Just like I do.
What is it?
What's their own purpose?
To be a chicken.
To live its life.
And to accomplish what?
To accomplish the beauty of Hashem's creation.
The other beings are...
Jeremiah was in the base of Migdash, right?
Yeah.
And he made sure every day the Kabanets were slaughtered and killed, right?
Jeremiah was against the animal sacrifice.
Oh, he was against it, right?
Yes, just like Hosea.
Show me.
I told you.
I don't care what you say.
Jeremiah 7.
Show us.
Pull it up on your phone.
Jeremiah 7:22.
No, this isn't even for my channel.
I want to say the main thing.
We cover a lot of this stuff.
Do you want to be on camera?